<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<problem>


<strong><font size="3">
        There are 5 Questions on this Quiz, and you have 25 minutes to complete it.  <br/><br/>
        You have two attempts for each part of the question (unless indicated otherwise)<br/><br/>
        Questions on this quiz will be hidden after you submit a correct response (first try), or if you used up your 2 attempts. <br/><br/>(Correct/incorrect status of the 2nd attempt will not be given, and your answer will be graded after everyone has completed the quiz)<br/> <br/>
               Make sure you submit each answer separately . <br/><br/>  Good Luck!  </font> </strong>
<hr/>
<br/>
<strong>Constants and Equations: </strong>
<br/>
<br/>
<td>c=λν</td> <td>    E=hν</td> <td></td>
<td>      ΔE= - 2.178x10<sup>-18</sup>J(1/n<sub>f</sub><sup>2</sup> - 1/n<sub>i</sub><sup>2</sup>)</td>
<br/>
<td>c=2.998x10<sup>8</sup> m/s </td><td>    h=6.626x10<sup>-34</sup> J s </td> <td>   &amp;nbspN<sub>A</sub>=6.022x10<sup>23</sup></td>
<br/>
<hr/>
<a name="11"></a>
  
      


1.  For the following statements, 

<br/>
<br/>
<br/><b>False:</b> 
            One mole of cesium nitride (Cs<sub>3</sub>N) has 7 grams of elemental nitrogen atom.
        
<br/><b>True:</b> 
            The unit for the molar mass of a compound is grams/mole
        
<br/><b>True:</b> 
            One mole of iron(III) sulfate, Fe<sub>2</sub>(SO<sub>4</sub>)<sub>3</sub>, contains 3 moles of sulfur
        
<br/><b>False:</b> 
            The mass of an element is the number of protons plus the number of electrons.
        
<br/>
<br/><hr/><br/>
<a name="14"></a>
          
2.  Your answer for the following calculation should contain how many significant figures?  <br/>(7.255+6.8350)/(80.705*1.4326)=  
<br/>
<br/>
<b> 5  </b>
<br/>
<br/>
<hr/><br/>
<a name="17"></a>
        
          
3. Children's Tylenol comes in a liquid suspension that has 160. mg acetominophen per teaspoon and is often used to reduced fever.  The recommended dosage for a child that weighs 95 lbs is 3.0 teaspoon.  How many mL does a child (with that weight) would need to take for a fever? <br/>(1 teaspoon=0.167 oz, 1 oz=29.6 mL)  
<br/>
<br/>
<b> 15  </b> mL

                

    <br/>
<hr/>
<br/>
<a name="20"></a>
  

    4.  Calculate the energy involved when the electron in a hydrogen atom undergoes this transition:  n=2 to n=5
    <br/>(Please include proper signs for this one, use scientific notations for your answer, i.e. 102 should be 1.02e2)
    <br/>
<b> 4.574×10<sup>-19</sup> </b>J
    

         
    
    <br/><hr/><br/>
<a name="23"></a>
          
	
5. Determine the starting value of n, if an electron in a hydrogen atom absorbs a photon with a frequency of 7.547E+11 kHz, and ends at n=7 energy level



 <br/>
<b> 2  </b>
<br/>
<hr/>
<hr/>


</problem>